Guide to the Josephine Herbst Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Other Papers, 1866-1969, undated; Series III; 12.62; (28 boxes)
  - Other Papers
    - Unsorted notes, writing fragments, and small notebooks, 1921-1969; 8 (Box 108)
      I am ambivalent to remove the folder contents since they may be together for some reason
    - Material removed from books in Herbst's personal library, 6 (Box 113)
    - Printed material collected by Herbst on a range of subjects
      - Printed material, 15 (Box 114)
      - Printed material, 14 (Box 115)
      - Printed material, 6 (Box 116)
      - Printed material, 24 (Box 117)
      - Printed material, 5 (Box 118)
      - Printed material, 6 (Box 119)
      - Printed material, 5 (Box 120)
- Frey and Herbst Family Papers, 1799-1913; Series IV; 4.86; (12 boxes)
  Related Archival Materials note
  Additional Herbst family correspondence is in Series I. Correspondence.
  Frey and Herbst Family Papers includes correspondence between various members of the Frey family, Herbst family papers, scrapbooks, and printed material.
  - Correspondence with
    - Effley, Alice Jay, 1821-1881; 41 (Box 121)
    - Frey, Joshua and Mary Anne, 1799-1881; 43 (Box 122)
    - Frey, Joseph, 1812-1871; 15 (Box 123)
    - Frey, Mary, 1817-1883; 28 (Box 124)
    - Frey, Mary, 1875-1882; 37 (Box 125)
    - Frey, Mary, 1871-1902; 37 (Box 126)
    - Frey, Priscilla, 1863-1877; 29 (Box 127)
    - Frey family correspondence, 1809-1899, undated; 91 (Box 128)
  - Herbst family financial papers and maps, 1843-1883; 5 (Box 129)
  - "The Girl Graduate: Her Own Book" scrapbook, Helen Herbst, 1913 (Box 130)
  - Scrapbook, 1861-1878 (Box 131)
    Bound volume with various markings and use. Includes Mary Frey's scrapbook, "Monthly Report, Boys & Girls, No. 3 Primary School of the 17th Section, First School District of Pennsylvania," and "Catalogue for Treasurer of University Female Institute of Lewisburg, Pennsylvania 1972"
  - Printed material, undated; 14 (Box 132)
- Restricted Fragile, 0.21; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Untitled, undated; 1; The program ends abruptly. There is static on the recording. There is high background noise on the tape. The program is distorted at times. There are speed fluctuations about halfway through the recording. (Box 134, Item barcode 39002091399270)